<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[weddings with jody]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[weddings with jody]]></description>
        <link>http://revjody.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 02:56:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://revjody.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 02:41:55 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Congratulations! You are Getting Married!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c1273a0e-d601-4a4f-a91e-1ccf7518b425.jpg" title="me" alt="rev. jody">,<h1>Congratulations! You are Getting Married!</h1>,<p>If youʼve found me here, chances are you are looking for a wedding officiant, someone to distill your precious love into words that speak of your unique connection and potential as a couple. You are hoping for a ceremony that expresses your joy, excitement and the reverence you have for your meeting. You’re excited to be joined together as life partners in marriage, one of the most profound expressions of relationship and love on this planet. You know in your heart you have made a brave but easy decision to marry and you want to share this milestone with your most precious family and friends…</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://revjody.com/congratulations-you-are-getting-married/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0b6278ff-628a-44b4-a20f-904262418c38</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 02:44:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A little more about my work.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5200054f-fb56-4134-a957-4b49aab8c49b.jpg">,<h1>A little more about my work.</h1>,<p>I am an ordained Interfaith and Interspiritual Minister who has been officiating weddings, vow renewels memorials, and baby blessings for over 10 years from coast to coast and around the world. I am also a spiritual counselor, parent coach and life coach who services individuals, couples and families. I have married couples in formal and informal settings of 4 to 400, indoor and outdoor, in backyards, on beaches and in a wide variety of venues. Iʼve done countless weddings in NYC, along the waterfront in Jersey City and Hoboken, where I live, as well as in the Hudson Valley…</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://revjody.com/a-little-more-about-my-work/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2790663a-bfbf-43cd-aa51-44f64f53196c</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 02:48:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>